Guide to the Harland Bartholomew and Associates planning reports, 1944-1990.
Harland Bartholomew and Associates planning reports
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Harland Bartholomew and Associates planning reports, 1944-1990.
6400
Harland Bartholomew and Associates.
6.4 cubic ft.
Printed Materials, Publications, Reports
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
This collection consists of planning reports and printed information created and used by the office of Harland Bartholomew and Associates.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Harland Bartholomew was born near Boston, Massachusetts in 1889 in the community of Stoneham, though his family moved shortly thereafter to a farm in New Hampshire. Although he enrolled in Rutgers civil engineering program, due to lack of funds, Bartholomew left after two years. He obtained work at the New York District of the Corps of Engineers then with E.P. Goodrich, a civil engineer active in the "city efficient" approach to city planning. There, Bartholomew was assigned to Newark, New Jersey, where he would be involved in preparing a city plan. Next, Bartholomew worked as a consultant and wrote about the new field of American city planning. In 1915, he moved to St. Louis, where he was hired to prepare a comprehensive city plan. By 1919, Bartholomew had enough expertise to found Harland Bartholomew Associates and hired architects, civil engineers and landscape architects to assist him in preparing comprehensive city plans for local governments. During the period of his greatest professional contributions, 1919-1962, Bartholomew carried on a three-part career simultaneously. He was Director of Planning at Newark, 1913-1916, at St. Louis, 1916-1953 and Washington, 1953-1962. Simultaneously, he was partner-in-charge of Harland Bartholomew and Associates for 42 years from 1919 to 1961. Finally, Bartholomew became a teacher of city planning at a number of American colleges.
More information about Bartholomew's career can be found in the accession folder, and in Harland Bartholomew: His Contributions to American Urban Planning by Eldridge Lovelace, 1993.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
This collection consists of planning reports and printed information created and used by the office of Harland Bartholomew and Associates. States represented in these reports include: Alabama, Arkansas, California, Delaware, Florida, Georgia, Indiana, Kentucky, Minnesota, Mississippi, Missouri, Nebraska, New Jersey, New York, Ohio, South Dakota, Tennessee, Virginia, Washington, and the District of Columbia.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Harland Bartholomew and Associates.
Subjects:
City planning--United States.; City planning--Missouri--St. Louis.; Regional planning--United States.; Regional planning--Missouri--St. Louis.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Traffic Access Study For Modifications To Proposed Parking Deck 3 At Eighth Avenue And Nineteenth Street South For The University Of Birmingham, Alabama (2 copies), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Public Works Program And Administration A Part Of The Comprehensive Plan, Birmingham, Alabama, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Planning Study For Lower Income Neighborhoods City Of Birmingham, Alabama, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Planning Study For Lower Income Neighborhoods City Of Birmingham, Alabama (draft copy), 1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Technical Report B, Transit Usage Analysis And Model Development, Birmingham [Alabama]-Jefferson County Regional Transportation Study, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Proposed Subdivision Regulations, Birmingham, Alabama, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Environmental Impact Assessment, Downtown Post Office Station Location, Montgomery, Alabama, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Major Street Plan, Mountain Brook, Alabama, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Fort Smith [Arkansas] Urban Area Study, Volume One, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Fort Smith [Arkansas] Urban Area Study, Volume Two, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Final Report On Community Renewal Plan, Hot Springs, Arkansas, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Delaware Water, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Master Plan For Balboa Park, San Diego, California (*), 1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Draft Copy, Preliminary Delaware Coastal Zone Plan, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Preliminary Comprehensive Development Plan [Delaware], 1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- A Proposal For A Transportation Study For The City Of Newark, Delaware, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Comprehensive Development Plan, Sussex County, Delaware, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Ocean Highway, Fenwick Island To Bethany Beach, Delaware, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- A Report Upon An Approach To The Mass Transportation Problem For The District Of Columbia, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Amenity, Metropolitan Dade County, Florida, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Report Upon A General Plan for the Shopping Center, Bal Harbour, Florida, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- A Report On Community Facilities, Clearwater, Florida, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- A Report on Housing And Public Utilities, Clearwater, Florida, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- General Land Use Master Plan, Metropolitan Dade County, Florida (*), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Prelimiary Land Use Plan [Metropolitan Dade County, Florida], 1960 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Preliminary Recommended Zoning Regulations For Metropolitan Dade County, Florida, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- A Report on Public Works, City Of Fort Pierce, Florida, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- The Comprehensive Plan, City Of Fort Pierce, Florida, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Jacksonville Traffic Control System [Florida], 1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Proposal For Professional Services, City Of Jacksonville, Florida, Downtown Development Authority, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Proposal For Engineering Services, City Of Jacksonville, Florida, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Transportation And The City, Excerpts From Architectural Forum, October, 1963, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- A Report on Public Works Program, City Of Miami Beach, Florida, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Part 1, The Comprehensive Plan, City Of Naples, Florida, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Zoning Ordinance, Pasco County, Florida, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Preliminary U.S. 19 Corridor Study, Pasco County, Florida, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- U.S. 19 Corridor Study, Pasco County, Florida, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Zoning Code, City Of Pompano Beach, Florida, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Comprehensive City Planning Report For Pompano Beach, Florida, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Bicycle Facilities Plan For The Sarasota-Bradenton Urban Area [Florida], 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Southeast Florida Transit Corridor Study, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- A Preliminary Report Upon Capital Improvement Program And Planning Administration, Surfside, Florida, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Community Facilities And Housing, A Part Of The Comprehensive Plan, Vero Beach, Florida, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Albany Civic Arena, Traffic Impact, Albany, Georgia, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Shannon Mall Traffic Study [Atlanta, Georgia], 1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Ball Ground Georgia, Land Use And Development Controls: I. Zoning Ordinance, II. Subdivision Regulations, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Ball Ground, Georgia, Comprehensive Plan, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Canton, Georgia, Land Use And Development Controls: I. Zoning Ordinance, II. Subdivision Regulations, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Canton, Georgia, Comprehensive Plan, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Cherokee County, Georgia, Comprehensive Plan Summary (2), 1064 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Cherokee County, Georgia, Land Use And Development Controls: I. Zoning Ordinance, II. Subdivision Regulations, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Central Business District Plan, Dalton, Georgia, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Zoning Ordinance, City Of Decatur, Georgia, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Population Trends, Economic Base, Land Use Analysis - A Part Of The Land Use Plan, Decatur, Georgia, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- A Report On Development Of A County Governmental Center, Dekalb County-Decatur, Georgia, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Holly Springs, Georgia, Land Use And Development Controls: I. Zoning Ordinance, II. Subdivision Regulations, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Holly Springs, Georgia, Comprehensive Plan, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- A Comprehensive Report On The Sanitary Sewerage System, Marietta Urban Area, Marietta, Georgia, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Zoning Ordinance, Ringgold, Georgia, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- A Report On Land Use And Zoning, Toccoa, Georgia, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Waleska, Georgia, Land Use And Development Controls: I. Zoning Ordinance, II. Subdivision Regulations, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Existing Land Use Survey And Analysis, West Point, Georgia, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Community Facilities Plan, Neighborhood Analysis And Major Thoroughfare Plan, West Point, Georgia, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- The Comprehensive Plan, West Point, Georgia, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Economic Base And Population Study And Future Land Use Plan, West Point, Georgia, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Public Improvements Program And Continuing Planning Program, West Point, Georgia, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Subdivision Regulations, West Point, Georgia, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Urban Fringe Area Study, West Point, Georgia, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Zoning Ordinance, West Point, Georgia, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Economic Survey For The Proposed Burns Harbor in Indiana, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Central Lafayette Renewal Plan [Indiana], 1969 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Proposed Zoning Regulations, Delaware County, Indiana, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Major Streets and Parking, Muncie Indiana, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Land Use And Revised Zoning Regulations, Muncie, Indiana, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Public Services, Muncie, Indiana, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Amended Zoning Ordinance, Muncie, Indiana, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- The Comprehensive Plan, Muncie, Indiana, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Campus Access And Traffic Operations Study, University Of Notre Dame, St. Joseph County, Indiana, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Operations Procedural Manual, St. Joseph County [Indiana], 1966 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Operations Procedure Manual, South Bend Urban Area {Indiana}, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- An Operational Residential Growth Model Developed for and Applied to The South Bend, Indiana Urban Area, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Appraisal Guidelines, Louisville Parks [Kentucky], 1965 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Fringe Area Study For Murray, Kentucky, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- An Urban Design Study For The Central Renewal Area In Duluth, Minnesota, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Proposal for Professional Services I-35 E Location Study, Phases II and III, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Areawide Waste Treatment Management Plan, Economic, Social, and Land Use Interim Output, Mississippi Arkansas Tennessee Council of Governments/Memphis Delta Development District, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Long Range Development Plan, Delta and Pine Land Company, Scott, Mississippi, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Sanitary Sewerage System, Leland Mississippi, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Official Comprehensive Plan, Bowling Green, Missouri, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Preliminary Report Population and Land Use, Bridgeton, Missouri, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- A Final Report Upon The Capital Improvement Program and Planning Implementation, Cape Girardeau, Missouri, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- A Preliminary Report Upon The Comprehensive Plan, Cape Girardeau, Missouri, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- The Comprehensive Plan, Cape Girardeau, Missouri, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Preliminary Report, Comprehensive Plan, Charleston, Missouri, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Parking & Traffic Study, University of Missouri, Columbia, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- A Preliminary Report Upon The Capital Improvement Program and Planning Implementaion, Crestwood, Missouri, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Preliminary Report Upon The Land Use, Zoning, and Subdivision Regulations, Crestwood, Missouri, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- A Report Upon The Consolidation Of The Cities Of Desloge, Elvins, Esther, Flat River, Leadington, RiverMines [Missouri], 1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Comprehensive Plan, De Soto, Missouri, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- A Report Upon The Business Area, Des Peres, Missouri, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- A Preliminary Report Upon The Capital Improvement Program and Planning Implementation, Ferguson, Missouri, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Preliminary Report Land Use, Population, Zoning And Subdivision Regulations, Ferguson, Missouri, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Preliminary Report Major Streets and Central Business District, Ferguson, Missouri, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Preliminary Report Schools, Parks and Public Buildings, Ferguson Missouri, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- The Comprehensive Plan, A Look Into Ferguson’s Future [Missouri], n.d. (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Annexation Plan, Flat River, Mo., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Land Use And Zoning, Florissant, Missouri, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Preliminary Report Upon Background Studies, Land Use Plan, And Zoning, Franklin County, Missouri, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- A Report Upon A Capital Improvement Program, Frontenac, Missouri, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- A Report Upon Major Streets and Recreation, Frontenac, Missouri, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- A Report Upon Public Buildings and Services, Frontenac, Missouri, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- A Report Upon West End Park Area, Frontenac, Missouri, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Campus Development Plan Part I - Space Use Analysis, Westminster College [Fulton, Missouri], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Campus Development Plan, Westminster College (Part II.) [Fulton, Missouri], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Annexation Plan, Jefferson City, Missouri, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Preliminary Report Upon Comprehensive Plan, Jefferson City, Missouri, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Revised Long-Range School Plan, Jefferson City Public Schools, Jefferson City, Missouri, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Economy And Population, Meramec, Rock and Joachim Townships, Jefferson County, Missouri, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Jefferson County Historic Sites Study [Missouri], 1968 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Land Use, Jefferson County, Missouri, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Major Highway Plan, Jefferson County, Missouri, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Preliminary Report Part III Water Facilities Plan, Jefferson County, Missouri, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Comprehensive Water And Sewer Plan, Jefferson County, Missouri (pp. 1-30), 1970 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Comprehensive Water And Sewer Plan, Jefferson County, Missouri(pp. 31-end [L-2]), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
- Ninth To Tenth On Main Street Project, Kansas City, Missouri, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Comprehensive Plan For Kennett, Missouri, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Park And Recreation Plan And Program, Kirkwood, Missouri, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- A Review Of The Revised Zoning Regulations For The City Of Ladue, Missouri, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- A Study Of Traffic Congestion, Lambert-St. Louis Airport Industrial Area [Missouri], 1959 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Preliminary Report Comprehensive Plan, Lebanon, Missouri, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Preliminary Report Comprehensive Plan, Mexico, Missouri, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Comprehensive Plan, Mexico, Missouri, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Preliminary Draft Upon The Proposed Zoning Ordinance, Mexico, Missouri, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- A Tentative Report Upon The Comprehensive Plan, Montgomery City, Missouri, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Traffic Analysis of Northeast Wentzville, Missouri, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Preliminary Report On The Comprehensive Plan For Parkville, Missouri, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Comprehensive Plan For Parkville, Missouri, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- A Tentative Report Upon Zoning Ordinance And Subdivision Regulations, Perryville, Missouri, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Preliminary Report On The Water And Sewerage Facilities, City Of Perryville, Missouri, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Investigation Of The Sanitary Sewage Collection System, Perryville, Missouri, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Comprehensive Plan, Perryville, Missouri, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- City Of Poplar Bluff [Missouri], A Preliminary Report On The Comprehensive Plan (2 different editions), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 20-21)
- A Preliminary Report Upon The Comprehensive Plan, Rock Port, Missouri, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- The Comprehensive Plan, Rock Port, Missouri, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- The Future Of St. James, Missouri, The Comprehensive Plan, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- A Parking Plan, University of Missouri, Saint Louis, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Specifications For First Phase Development, Faust County Park, Project Number 14D14, St. Louis County, Missouri, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Faust County Park Site Analysis [St. Louis County, Missouri], 1970 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Master Site Development Plan Faust County Park, St. Louis County, Missouri, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Faust County Park, St. Louis County, Missouri, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- 1959 Land Use Inventory, Saint Louis County, Missouri, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- A General Land Use Plan, Saint Louis County, Missouri, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Locks And Dam No. 26 (Replacement) Upper Mississippi River Basin, Mississippi River - Alton, Illinois, Missouri and Illinois, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 32-33)
- Comprehensive Plan, Sullivan Missouri, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Comprehensive Plan, Troy, Missouri, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Annexation Plan, Washington, Missouri, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- 1966 Supplement To The Webster Groves City Plan [Missouri], 1966 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Preliminary Estimate Of Complete Development Cost Jefferson Barracks National Cemetery [Missouri], 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Jefferson Barracks [Missouri], n.d. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Technical Report On The Development Plan Jefferson Barracks National Cemetery [Missouri], 1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Jefferson Barracks National Cemetery Memorial Amphitheater [Missouri], 1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Environmental Assessment Of The Undeveloped Property Jefferson Barracks National Cemetery [Missouri], 1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Comprehensive Plan, Bellevue, Nebraska, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Application For "Grant For Open-Space Land" By Lincoln, Nebraska, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- A Preliminary Report Upon The Comprehensive Plan, O’Neill, Nebraska, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Preliminary Report Comprehensive Plan, Schuyler, Nebraska, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Comprehensive Plan, Schuyler, Nebraska, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Preliminary Report Comprehensive Plan, York Nebraska, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Comprehensive Plan, York, Nebraska, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- The Setting For Regional Planning In New Jersey (*), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- A Preliminary Report On The Character Of The City And Past And Probable Future Population, East Orange, New Jersey, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Capital Expenditures & Administration, East Orange, New Jersey, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Housing & Zoning, East Orange, New Jersey, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Major Streets, East Orange, New Jersey, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- A Preliminary Report On A Proposed System Of Public Libraries For East Orange, New Jersey, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Suggested Procedure In Adoptimg The Master Plan For East Orange [New Jersey], 1949 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- The Master Plan For East Orange, New Jersey (*), 1950 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Impacts Of A Jet Airport In Morris County, New Jersey, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Master Plan And Program For A County Park System, Morris County, N.J., 1957 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Patterns Of General Development For Morris County {New Jersey}, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Refuse Disposal Study, Morris County, New Jersey, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- A Report Upon Alignment Of Federal Aid Interstate Route 104 (FAI-104), Morristown, New Jersey, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Background For A Plan 1963, Morristown, New Jersey, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- The Comprehensive Plan For Morristown, New Jersey (part two), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- A Study Of The Consolidation Of The School Systems Of Morristown And Morris Township [New Jersey], 1959 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Town Of Morristown, New Jersey, Master Plan, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Parking Survey And Program, Central Business District, Morristown, New Jersey, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Parking Survey And Recommended Program 1963 Central Business District, Morristown, New Jersey, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Parking Report, High Street - Park Place Area, Morristown, N.J., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Historic Morristown and the Morris Area, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Travel Patterns And Traffic Usage Interstate Route 287 In Vicinity Of Morristown, New Jersey, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- A Report On Airport Requirements And Sites In The Metropolitan New Jersey-New York Region (*), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Proposed Development Plan, Town Of Hamburg, N.Y., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Town Of Huntington Comprehensive Plan, Suffolk County, New York (*), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Survey Of The Potential Of The Community And Analysis Of The Impact Of A State Park And Parkway, Lloyd Harbor, New York, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Ogdensburg, New York, An Evaluation Of The Commercial, Residential, and Industrial Development Potential For The City Of Ogdensburg (*), 1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Basic Economic Information, Rochester, N.Y., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Comprehensive Plan, East Rochester, N.Y., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Design For The Future, Rochester-Monroe County Metropolitan Area [New York] (*), 1964 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Drainage Study Stage One, Rochester-Monroe County Metropolitan Area [New York] (*), 1962 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Shoreline Erosion Study, Lake Erie Shoreline, Lake County, Ohio, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Population And General Land Use - Ashtabula And Environs, Ashtabula, Ohio, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Economy Of The Area, Ashtabula, Ohio, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Housing, Ashtabula, Ohio, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Preliminary Report 1967 Comprehensive Plan, Blue Ash, Ohio, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- A Final Report Upon Land Use And Zoning, Major Thoroughfares, Subdivision Regulations, Bryan, Ohio, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Revised Subdivision Regulations, Bryan, Ohio, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Amended Zoning Ordinance, Bryan, Ohio, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Zoning Code, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Evaluation Of Stadium Sites In Hamilton County, Ohio, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Central Business District Urban Design Plan, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- A Tentative Report Upon The Comprehensive Plan, Grandview Heights, Ohio, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Revised Village Plan, Oxford, Ohio, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Comprehensive Plan, Tiffin, Ohio, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Summary Of The Comprehensive Plan, Tiffin, Ohio, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Economic Background, Population, Land Use And Zoning, Tiffin, Ohio, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Major Thoroughfares And The Central Business District, Tiffin, Ohio, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Schools, Parks, And Public Buildings, Tiffin, Ohio, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- A Tentative Report Upon Proposed Revised Zoning Regulations, Tiffin, Ohio, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Land Use And Zoning, Troy, Ohio, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Land Use And Zoning, Brookings, South Dakota, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Highway Access Areas In Tennessee (*), 1962 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- An Outline Of Techniques And Procedures For An Urban Area Transportation Study [Tennessee], n.d. (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Cost-Revenue Aspects Annexation Of The Bemis Area To The City Of Jackson, Tennessee, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Continuous Planning Program, Memphis Urban Area [Tennessee], 1962 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Interstate Route 40 Memphis CBD Interchange Study [Tennessee], 1965 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Improvement Plans And Programs, Housing and Community Development Priority Areas, Memphis, Tennessee, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 32)